itninja.com 2012-06-01

# ITNinja Privacy Policy

ITNinja Privacy Policy
The following statement describes the privacy policy relating to the ITNinja web
site (the "Site") operated by Dell, Inc. ("Dell" or "we"). Dell is committed to user
privacy in all of its communications regarding its products and services. If you
provide Dell with information via the ITNinja website, it will be treated according
to this policy. Dell encourages you to read this policy before interacting with the
website. By providing any personal information to Dell via the ITNinja web site or
e-mail addresses, you agree to these terms.
The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of the following:
   •    What kind of information, including any personally identifiable information,
          is collected
   •    Who collects the information
   •    How the information is used
   •    With whom the information may be shared
   •    What choices are available to you regarding its collection, use, and
          distribution
   •    The security procedures that are in place to protect the information
   •    How you can correct inaccuracies in the information
Information We Collect
Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Non-personally identifiable information
is information that, by itself, cannot be tracked to a specific individual. Dell may
collect non-personally identifiable information while you are visiting the
Site. While providing services and features, Dell may collect web surfing data
such as your IP address, web pages on the Site that have you visited, time and
date, the web site you came through to reach the Site, and whether or not you
clicked on any links while at the Site. We may use different types of technologies
to collect this information, including cookies and single-pixel GIFs.
If your browser is configured to accept the cookies, these cookies will be used to
recognize your computer when you revisit the Site to provide you with a better
web surfing experience; for example, it allows us to learn how you use the Site
and to show you information we think you would want to see. If you wish, you
can configure your browser to block cookies; however, your ability to access
certain portions of the Site may be affected.
Links to third parties may be displayed on the Site. These third parties may use
cookies or other technologies to collect information when you are visiting their
web sites. The information advertisers or other third parties collect is governed
by their individual privacy policies, not by Dell’s privacy policy.
Personally Identifiable Information. While providing various services or features,
we may ask you to provide personal information. For example, if you choose to
register at the Site, you may be asked to provide your name, email address,

telephone number, company, title, password and/or username. If you choose to
use the Site, create a profile or post information on our question and answer
system, blogs, links, and software library, you may elect to provide information,
such as your name, telephone number, street address, age, text, messages,
feedback, images, suggestions, photos, birthday, icon, links to web sites,
information regarding what products interest you, product information, bugs, and
other comments, or other content ("User Submissions").
Use of the Information We Collect
Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Dell may use non-personally
identifiable information collected to improve the quality of Dell’s services; for
example, by diagnosing service or technology problems, by assessing and
maintaining security, by increasing ad placements on web sites that are
generating more web traffic, by presenting you with information that we think you
would be interested in seeing, or by allowing you to log in or access your profile
information automatically. We may also use the information to count and
recognize returning users.
Dell may use non-personally identifiable information collected to determine user
demographics, interests, and behavior and may market Dell products by sharing
non-personally identifiable information with potential customers or partners. Dell
also may provide your non-personally identifiable information to contractors so
that they can perform services for us.
Use of Personally Identifiable Information. User Submissions, profile
information, including without limitation your username, email address, and
location may be viewable by others. Dell does not intentionally directly provide
personally identifiable information to partners, except if you provide personally
identifiable information as part of an inquiry about products or services provided
by one of the partners. In that case, we will provide that information to that
partner so that they may attempt to provide you with information regarding the
products or services about which you inquired.
If you provide us your email address when requesting information or when
signing up for user communities, newsletters, or other services, we may send
you email messages to communicate with you or to provide you information that
we think you would like to see.
If Dell shares any of the information collected from you with a third party, the third
party's use of that information will then be governed by the third party's privacy
policy.
If you provide personally identifiable information for your profile or other User
Submissions, other users of the Site will have access to this information.
Other Sharing of Information Dell may release any information about any user,

including personally identifiable information, if in its sole discretion, release is
appropriate to comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement,
court order, or any investigation. Dell also may release information to protect its
rights, property, or other interests, including those of its customers or users or to
prevent illegal activities or violations of Dell’s ITNinja Terms of Service
Agreement (available at www.itninja.com/terms_of_service.pdf).
In the event that Dell, in whole or in part, establishes a partnership with another
company, or is acquired by or merged with another company or enters
bankruptcy, collected information may be transferred to the partner or the
acquiring or merging company.
Deletions/Corrections/Opt-Out
You can delete your account and profile by contacting us directly at
support@itninja.com. You may also change your profile information by logging in
to your user profile.
Dell also allows users who choose to provide personally identifiable information
on their profile to edit their profile to ensure that it is correct and up-to-date. We
may use your email address to send you messages notifying you of important
changes to the Site, services, and special offers. If you do not want to receive
such email messages, you may opt out by sending an email message to
support@itninja.com or by sending mail to the following postal address:
Dell KACE
Attn: Bob Kelly
PO Box 639
Haymarket, VA 20168
Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates,
improvements, or special offers.
Child Protection
Dell does not offer services to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In
compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we
receive from people we believe to be children under 13 will be purged from our
database.
International Users
The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users
in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United
States, the laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and
disclosure may differ from United States laws. Be advised that through your
continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and
our Terms of Services, you are transferring your personal information to the
United States and you consent to that transfer.

Security
Dell makes efforts to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the
collected information. Be aware, however, that the Internet is not 100%
secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted
over the Internet, and we accept no liability for any disclosure. Many areas of the
Site are password-protected. To increase the security of the Site, please do not
share your passwords with anyone.
Links to Other Web Sites
The Site may contain links to other web sites. In addition, User Submissions
might contain links to other web sites. Dell is not responsible for the privacy
practices or the content of any third party web sites that may be linked to the
Site.
Modifications
This privacy policy replaces any previous privacy policies formerly posted on the
Site. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the
changes on this web page and any such changes are immediately effective upon
posting. We also may notify you about changes to the privacy policy by sending
you a notice to your email address or by placing a notice on the Site. Please
check the effective date at the top of this page to determine if the privacy policy
has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of the Site
following posting of this or any updated privacy policy will constitute your
acceptance
